<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on K Ring Technologies Ltd</title>
    <link>https://kring.co.uk/works/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on K Ring Technologies Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 12:36:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kring.co.uk/works/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Changeover</title>
      <link>https://kring.co.uk/works/cloudflare-changeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 12:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kring.co.uk/works/cloudflare-changeover/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This site is hosted on CloudFlare with workers for lambda style JS server side&#xA;scripting. The login feature uses this. I&amp;rsquo;m moving my DNS to this site soon.&#xA;I can then shutdown the old development server or repurpose it for experimental&#xA;use. I may transfer some of the text articles over, as I have done a &lt;code&gt;wget&lt;/code&gt; of&#xA;the old site. It used &lt;code&gt;WordPress&lt;/code&gt;, and I am over my desire to use PHP, and&#xA;keeping up using a bit of an open-source news bane.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Login</title>
      <link>https://kring.co.uk/works/google-login/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 12:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kring.co.uk/works/google-login/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The google login is in progress and does not yet work. Your email is not on the&#xA;list, so no point in trying yet. Also there is as yet no logout link although&#xA;for testers the logout happens after one day. There is also nothing happening&#xA;in terms of extra features for logging in. This should change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A joypad adapter to tunnel through into a container to use with&#xA;&lt;code&gt;doris.nvim&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A reverse proxy to tunnel &lt;code&gt;nvim&lt;/code&gt; out of the container, and use the&#xA;external browser as a &lt;code&gt;https&lt;/code&gt; connection to the internet, so that &lt;code&gt;doris.nvim&lt;/code&gt;&#xA;may run some kind of BBS text service TUI.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s things to be done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
