<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on K Ring Technologies Ltd</title>
    <link>https://kring.co.uk/tags/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on K Ring Technologies Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:18:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kring.co.uk/tags/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://kring.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kring.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;circa-2024&#34;&gt;Circa 2024&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;K Ring Technologies became a Ltd company after a number of years being a&#xA;&amp;ldquo;trading as&amp;rdquo; name for the founder&amp;rsquo;s contracting internet and software work.&#xA;Work became infrequent and declined over the COVID 19 years, and is just an&#xA;R and D shell circa 2024. It has no financial liabilities to creditors, and so&#xA;it was decided to continue the company for the future. The founder Simon Jackson&#xA;has an interest in computer technology and programming, and maintains a&#xA;deep interest in physics, chemistry and mathematics. It is not uncommon for him&#xA;to watch highly technical presentations on many science subjects, and he even&#xA;has his own theoretical physics theories which really started with&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Uncertain Geometry&lt;/strong&gt;. That theory being about consequences of theories of&#xA;motion independent of mass, using velocity as a phase space dimension along&#xA;with position. The 13 D (26 degrees of freedom) have possibilities.&#xA;He also has a composite gluon theory where 2 half gluon particles combine in&#xA;pairs to replace the &amp;ldquo;approximate&amp;rdquo; 8 gluon varieties. He maintains an interest&#xA;in data compression algorithms, AI and some methods of mathematical integration.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
